Plane ticket, painting,
it all points to Montreal.
What is this place?
"We were right about the Company.
The world is in danger. Adam. "
Please, tell me who I am.
What the future holds.
We’ll figure it out.
-We’re in New York.
-Where is everyone?
It’s an evacuation order.
June 14th, 2008.
This is next year.
This thing we could do,
it only begins at reading minds...
and then it becomes so much more.
My dad can put a thought
into anyone’s head.
Now we know why Molly calls him
the nightmare man.
-It’s Bob.
-He runs the Company.
-Looks like he’s next.
-You sure you’ll be able to cure me?
In exchange, we’re going to want
a little something from you.
-Hello, Dr. Suresh.
-So you’re...
Your new partner.
Claire?
Oh my god!
-Did you see her face?
-Somebody could have seen us!
Relax! Just think of it
as a lesson in humility.
-What’s on your neck?
-Last thing I remember is...
this man stepping out
of the bushes calling my name.
What are you talking about?
What man?